http://www.shenzhenknives.com/pages/privacy-legal

Your Consent
By visiting or shopping on our site, you consent to the conditions outlined below.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of cookies enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of Google's cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needsTo improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactions:Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature:To send periodic emails:The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and clicking on the "Login" link.
Terms and Conditions
This section establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website below this section.
Changes to our Privacy policy or Terms & Conditions
If we decide to change our privacy policy or terms and conditions, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 04-10-12.
Warranty and Limitation of Liability
NOTE: If you are suffering from insomnia or other sleep disorder, we recommend reading the following legal, and warranty and limitation of liability section.
Subject to the limitations below, TAF International (dba Shenzhen Knives) warrants its products to be free from defects in materials or workmanship under normal usage for ninety (90) days after original purchase date. Provided that the defective product is returned to TAF International during the warranty period, postage pre-paid, together with valid, dated proof of purchase, TAF International will, at its sole option, repair or replace the defective product free of charge or refund the original purchase price less shipping costs. This warranty extends only to the original purchaser and is not transferable. This warranty does not cover defects resulting from (a) commercial use; (b) normal wear and tear; improper use, maintenance or storage; or misuse, accidents or neglect. TAF International makes no warranty for products modified by the buyer or subject to misuse or neglect.
WHERE PERMITTED, THE PROVISIONS OF THIS LIMITED WARRANTY ARE THE COMPLETE AND EXCLUSIVE STATEMENT OF WARRANTY WHICH TAF INTERNATIONAL PROVIDES AND ARE IN LIEU OF ANY OTHER WRITTEN WARRANTY, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WRITTEN OR ORAL, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WILL BE LIMITED TO THE DURATION OF THIS LIMITED WARRANTY. Notwithstanding the above, where applicable, if you qualify as a "consumer" under the Magnuson-Moss Warranty Act, then you may be entitled to any implied warranties allowed by law for the period of the express Limited Warranty as stated above. Some states do not allow limitations on how long an implied Limited Warranty lasts, so the above limitation may not apply to you.
IN NO EVENT, WILL TAF INTERNATIONAL BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF TIME, INCONVENIENCE, COMMERCIAL LOSS, LOST PROFITS OR SAVINGS, OR OTHER INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR SPECIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE SUCH PRODUCT, TO THE FULL EXTENT SUCH MAY BE DISCLAIMED BY LAW. IN NO EVENT WILL TAF INTERNATIONAL'S LIABILITY EXCEED THE ORIGINAL PURCHASE PRICE OF THE PRODUCT. Some states and jurisdictions do not allow the limitation or exclusion of incidental or consequential damages, and thus, the limitations on damages may not apply to you. This warranty gives you specific legal rights, and you may have other rights which vary from state to state.
TAF INTERNATIONAL DOES NOT PROVIDE ANY WARRANTY COVERAGE UNLESS CLAIMS ARE SUBMITTED AS FOLLOWS: To request warranty service, contact TAF International via the contact information at www.shenzhenknives.com. If TAF International determines that a repair or replacement is required, you will be asked to provide your name, address, phone number, email, and order number. Products returned to TAF International must be properly packaged, with the delivery charges prepaid via a shipping method that provides for tracking of your package, to our mailing address. A product confirmed as defective (as described in the TAF International warranty) may be replaced with an identical item or, if the item is no longer available, with a comparable product or refund of original purchase price less shipping costs. All costs associated with the shipment of the product are your responsibility.
THIS WARRANTY ONLY APPLIES TO PURCHASERS WHO HAVE PURCHASED THE PRODUCT DIRECTLY FROM www.shenzhenknives.com or TAF International, it does not apply to 3rd party sellers of Shenzhen Knives. Except where restricted by law, this warranty applies only to the original purchaser of a new product.
IN ADDITION, TO THE PRODUCT LIMITED WARRANTY AND LIABILITY, TAF INTERNATIONAL SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, AND IN PARTICULAR TAF INTERNATIONAL SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF REVENUE, OR LOSS OF USE, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THIS WEB SITE OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN IT, WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARISE IN CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, TORT, UNDER STATUTE, IN EQUITY, AT LAW, OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF TAF INTERNATIONAL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW FOR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, THEREFORE SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS IS INAPPLICABLE.
Applicable Law
By visiting Shenzhenknives.com, you agree that applicable federal law, and the laws of the state of Hawaii without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these terms and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Shenzhen Knives .
Copyright
All content included on this site, is the property of Shenzhen Knives and protected by United States and international copyright laws.
Risk of Loss
All items purchased from Shenzhen Knives are made pursuant to a shipment contract. The risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier.
Policies, changes and severability
We reserve the right to make changes to our site, policies, and terms and conditoins at any time. If any of these conditions shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy and terms and conditions you may contact us using the information below:www.shenzhenknives.comShenzhen Ceramic Knives3615 Harding Avenue #409Honolulu, HI 96816866-983-2228
